<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nikola Marcetic</title>
    <link>https://www.nmarcetic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nikola Marcetic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.nmarcetic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://www.nmarcetic.com/work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:12:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nmarcetic.com/work/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s all about my journey, skills, how I like to work, and research.
How I work I enjoy a remote lifestyle for the last six years. I believe in distributed teams and remote team cultures. It is the synonym for productivity and high-quality teams with top talents, most important a perfect life balance and happiness.
I use technology to solve problems and build digital products. Ideas and innovations are the biggest motivation for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.nmarcetic.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:11:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nmarcetic.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get in touch
Email: nmarcetic86@gmail.com
Ready to talk? Feel free to book a time slot that suits best for you,
Schedule 30min Zoom call</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi, I&#39;m Nikola. 👋</title>
      <link>https://www.nmarcetic.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:04:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.nmarcetic.com/about/</guid>
      <description>A passionate, open-source leader and contributor, Co-author of the industry-leading Mainflux open-source IoT platform. For over ten years now, in the tech industry, with strong leadership skills and experience in technologies around distributed systems and cloud computing.
Last six years, As an open-source evangelist, I am focused on industrial IoT, automation, and secure data exchange. I was working closely with Enterprises in designing mission-critical, real-life IoT solutions.
These days I am working on new ideas with the primary mission of building community first open IoT governance with shared ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
