<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nikola Marcetic</title>
    <link>https://nmarcetic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nikola Marcetic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://nmarcetic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>🧬 Lab</title>
      <link>https://nmarcetic.com/lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:12:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmarcetic.com/lab/</guid>
      <description>This page is a snapshot of what I build, how I think, and what I’m currently exploring. A mix of craft, engineering philosophy, and the systems I spend my time improving.
How I Work I’ve been working remotely for years, and I genuinely believe distributed teams build the best systems. Autonomy, clarity, ownership, and deep focus matter more than offices ever will.
I like working with people who move fast, communicate openly, and keep their ego out of the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🔗 Connect</title>
      <link>https://nmarcetic.com/connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:11:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmarcetic.com/connect/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s get in touch
Email: nmarcetic86@gmail.com
Telegram: @nmarcetic
Ready to talk? Feel free to book a time slot that suits best for you,
Schedule 30min meet call</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>👋 I&#39;m Nikola.</title>
      <link>https://nmarcetic.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:04:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmarcetic.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I’ve spent more than a decade building reliable, scalable, and secure systems across multiple industries.
I began my career in Web2, working on infrastructure and distributed systems, contributing to open-source projects long before stepping into the IoT world. Later, I became a co-author of the Mainflux open-source platform, a Linux Foundation project adopted as a backbone technology by enterprises such as Intel, Target, Nokia, and NOV, and presented at major industry events across Europe and Silicon Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
